# **Visatouch Deeying**

Phone: (+66) 85 345 7488

Email: visatouch@vi.satou.ch | Website: https://vi.satou.ch

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/visatouch">https://www.linkedin.com/in/visatouch</a> | GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/xerodotc">https://github.com/xerodotc</a>

## About me

My name is Visatouch Deeying. My nickname is Boat. I have interests and passions for innovations and technologies that will impact everyday life and improve our standard of living. Currently, I'm working as a software engineer at KASIKORN Business-Technology Group in Thailand. I have an experience in build and designing software architecture for projects within the company, and give advices about software architectures that I'm working on. I also joined a community within a company to brainstorm for a way to improve software development methodology such as providing software development guideline or boilerplate, or providing common library to reduce code duplication and effort.

# Work experiences

### KASIKORN Labs Co., Ltd. – Innovation Engineer

2019 - present

- Part of KASIKORN Business-Technology Group (KBTG).
- Mainly work on server-side and infrastructure of various innovation software projects within the company such as TAGTHAi, Eatable, and MAKE (please see the details in the projects section).

#### Faculty of Engineering, Chulalongkorn University – Teaching Assistant

2017 - 2019

- Involved in Computer System Architectures class and Computer Networks class.
- Prepare a hand-on laboratory and grade assignments.

#### Kinoshita's Laboratory, Tokyo University of Technology – Research Intern

2016

- Helped with a research about "Smartphone Authentication by Trace of Touch Operation".
- Created an Android application to collect data of touch details for an experiment and suggest possible methods for implementation in real devices.

## **Educations**

#### Chulalongkorn University – Master of Engineering in Computer Engineering

2017 - 2019

- Thesis Title: Desynchronization Communication System for Automatic Vehicle Platooning
- Publication: A study of vehicular desynchronization for platooning application (https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8359878/).
- Thesis Evaluation: Good

#### Chulalongkorn University – Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

2013 - 2017

- GPAX: 3.60 (1<sup>st</sup> Class Honors)
- Activities: Organizing ACM-ICPC contests within the university, responsible for managing contest system.

Visatouch Deeying Curriculum vitae

## **Skills**

#### **Programming Languages**

- Go: 2 years of experience
- Bash/Shell: 6 years of experience
- Other programming languages: Python, Kotlin, Dart, JavaScript, Java, C/C++.

### Other Software Development/Computer Skills

- Framework: Gin Web Framework, Chi router
- API integration: LINE API, K-Payment Gateway
- Database: SQL, MongoDB, Redis
- Cloud Platform: Google Cloud Platform, HUAWEI CLOUD
- DevOps Tools: Kubernetes, Jenkins, GitLab CI, Github Actions

#### Languages

- English (intermediate, TOEFL iBT 89 points)
- Japanese (beginner, JLPT N3 passed)
- Thai (native)

# **Projects**

TAGTHAi 2021 - present

- A travel guide application intended for tourists coming to Thailand.
- In the team, I work on server-side API with Go, Java, Kubernetes and Google Cloud Platform.
- In this project, I'm responsible for migrating an application to cloud service and develop new features
- For more details about the product, see <a href="http://www.tagthai.com">http://www.tagthai.com</a>.

#### SCHO\_OL Solutions (temporary name)

2020 - present

- A total solution for elementary or primary school, which provide activities tracking of the students for parents and can provide a forewarning for disease transmitted among the children and prevent further transmissions.
- Originally created for hackathon competition (LINE HACK 2020), and won the 1<sup>st</sup> runner-up prize for general public category.
- In the hackathon, I worked on a server-side API with Go running on Google App Engine, integrating with LINE API and LINE Beacon, also used Dialogflow for conversational interface.

Eatable 2019 - present

- A digital platform for restaurants where customers can make orders at the restaurant with their mobile phone via LINE LIFF Application, and can be used as a POS solution on the merchant side.
- In the team, I work on server-side API with Go, Kubernetes and HUAWEI Cloud.
- In this project, I designed an overall architecture of the application and build APIs as per designed.
- In the later stage, I transferred the knowledge about application's architecture to other co-workers and act as a technical advisor for this project, while I have to switch to other projects in the company.
- For more details about the product, see <a href="https://eatable.kasikornbank.com">https://eatable.kasikornbank.com</a> (in Thai language).

MAKE by KBank 2019

- A new generation of mobile banking experience, which have various distinct features that differentiate from traditional mobile banking.
- In the team, I worked on server-side API with Go, Kubernetes and Google Cloud Platform.
- In this project, I worked on the security component which act as an intermediary between a client and internal services, enhancing the application security to be compliant with bank's standard.
- For more details about the product, see <a href="https://www.kbtg.tech/makebank/index.html">https://www.kbtg.tech/makebank/index.html</a>.

More projects information are on LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/in/visatouch)